Jeonghyeok Park

+13918432034 | qkrwjdgur09@naver.com Shanghai

WeChat: Jeonghyeok1 | github.com/tmtmaj

Age: 28

Graduated with a master's degree in 2021. | Objective: Enginneering position in Natural Language Processing

Summary

Engineering graduate seeking an engineering position in natural language processing(NLP). 3+ years of research and implementation in NLP, including data mining/preprocessing, machine translation, pre-training language model, etc. Strong background in CNN, RNN, GAN, and experimental design experience using packages, like Pytorch, TensorFlow, Numpy, OpenNMT, Fairseq. 5+ years of programming experience with Python, Java, and C, and familiar with GPU/TPU programming and computer hardware.

Skills, Certifications & Others

- Skills: Python, Java, C, Aduino, Android Studio, PowerPoint, Excel, Word
- Certifications: Engineer Information Processing (Korean license)
- Languages: Native Korean, Chinese (New HSK6 Level 219), English (TOEIK795)
- Interests: Sing and play guitar

Education

KOREATECH Mar 2011 - Feb 2017

Information and Communication Engineering Bachelor

Cheonan City, South Korea

- GPA: 3.58/4.5
- Award: 1st prize in 2016 KOREATECH Capstone Design Competition, and Minister prize (Ministry of Trade, Industry and Energy of Korea) in 2016 E2FESTA(Engineering Education Festa)
- Scholarship: outstanding student scholarship in 2015 (all subjects are all A+)
- Related courses: C/Java programming language, communications engineering, electronic circuits, and data communications.

Shanghai Jiao Tong University

Sep 2017 - Mar 2021

Computer Science and Technology Master

Shanghai

- GPA: 2.87/4.0
- Internship: the editorial department of Shanghai Yuebo Advertising Co., Ltd. from June 2019 to February 2020
- Conference: PACLIC33 (Japan) in September 2019 and presented a paper presentation (poster session)
- Related courses: artificial intelligence, natural language processing, algorithm theory, advanced database technology, Chinese culture

Project Experiences

IT Convergence Guitar For Interactive Lesson (Title: GuitarSolo)

Nov 2015 - Nov 2016

Research members

Cheonan, South Korea

The goal of GuitarSolo is to provide users with an effective guitar learning environment through multiple functions.

- My work
- Develop android application program and data transmission algorithm between embedded system and application program
- 2. Find suitable sensors and design algorithms to improve the real-time recognition performance of guitars
- 3. Design and make models of special guitars (Guangzhou Delta Factory produces special guitars)
- 4. Design the main controller (Atmel'sCortex-M3familySAM3A8C) and develop embedded software (C/C++ language (ArduinoIDE))

Develop Android applications

Aug 2016 - Sep 2016

finish independently

Cheonan, South Korea

Entrusted by DAME, we developed Android applications related to metronome and guitar tuning.

Publications

Real-time Recognition of Guitar Performance Using Two Sensor Groups for Interactive Lesson

Yejin Shin, Jemin Hwang, Jeonghyeok Park, and Soonuk Seol. TEI '18 Proceedings of the Twelfth International Conference on Tangible, Embedded, and embodied Interaction.

Korean-to-Chinese Machine Translation using Chinese Character as Pivot Clue

Jeonghyeok Park and Hai Zhao. 33rd Pacific Asia Conference on Language, Information and Computation (PACLIC 33).

Collaborative Anomaly Detection for Internet of Things based on Federated Learning

Seongwoo Kim, He Cai, Cunqing Hua, Pengwenlong Gu, Wenchao Xu, Jeonghyeok Park. IEEE International Conference on Communication in China. August 09-11, 2020.